### Résumé Alvin Gregory Charles

Life @ Ratchada-Huay Kwang Condo, Pracharatbumphen rd, Huay Kwang Bangkok 10310

Mobile: 0863480050

Email: ac\_greg79@yahoo.com



#### **SUMMARY**

An individual who is well experienced in both online and offline marketing, has the ability to support superiors efficiently by carrying out directives of the business unit competently and independently. Particular strength in being a skilled communicator and team player, able to maintain cultural sensitivity and establish a good working rapport with colleagues and superiors in a diverse working environment.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Aware Corporation Limited**

Aware is one of Thailand's leading IT companies. From world-class software development teams to professional service and systems integration teams, Aware is positioned to address both the technical and business challenges for clients, and to deliver end-to-end technology solutions.

# Digital Marketing and Social Media Manager (Marketing Department)

Apr 2014 ~ Present

- Manage and build Aware's social media channels (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+, YouTube and Instagram)
- Implement digital marketing strategies that support marketing other business unit's objectives (social media and display advertising campaigns, electronic direct mails).
- Generate, edit, publish and share meaningful content (original text, images, video and graphics) that encourages community members to take social actions.
- Manage SEO and SEM activities to optimize site, boost page rankings and traffic.
- Build relationships with influencers and bloggers to build online presence (link building, copromotion activities).
- Manage and create content on Aware's corporate site, crafting blog contents and news releases.
- Work with teams to create offline and online marketing materials, manage trade shows, events and open house activities that can be shared on Aware's social media channels.
- Analyse and provide insights from social media analytics, Google analytics and sentiment reporting.
- Monitor and perform competitor analysis to gain insights on current trends.
- Implement social media policy and ensure that internal staff adhere to it.

#### Pajasalmi, Ruangkittikul & Associates, Limited (PR & Associates)

PR& Associates has extensive experience in Corporate Communications in Thailand & SE Asia. It provides a wide array of marketing and PR services with a global outreach to top global clients in Thailand and other regions of the world.

# Senior Marketing Manager (Digital Marketing and PR Communications Group)

Mar 2012 ~ Apr 2014

- Senior account manager of a large telecommunication client and also provide support to other global clients in terms of corporate and marketing communications. (BlackBerry, HP, Citibank, Hitachi and Canon)
- Implement digital marketing strategies, coordinating with stakeholders across the company

- to ensure its effectiveness.
- Work with the Product development team to ensure social media tools (FB apps, tabs and cover picture mock ups) are properly developed and implemented.
- Manage digital marketing campaigns and day-to-day activities. Duties include online advocacy, SEO, SEM, content management, community-outreach activities.
- Manage presence in social networking sites including Facebook, Twitter, and other similar community sites and seeding content into other social channels as needed.
- Analyse, review, and report on effectiveness of social media campaigns to maximize results.
- Craft press releases and corporate communications for global clients (Citibank, Hitachi and Canon)
- In charge of budget planning and payments for the department.
- Sole manager of the responsibilities and performance of the staff in the digital team.
- Responsible for business development with new clients and to expand work with existing clients.

#### **Citibank Singapore Limited**

Citibank Singapore is a subsidiary of Citigroup, one of the world's largest financial services organisations offering some of the world's leading range of financial services.

### **Brand and Digital Marketing Manager** (Brand Management and Marketing Department)

Jan 2009 ~ Mar 2012

- Promoting of various Citibank Credit Cards and promotions to all clients in Citibank through online and social platform (Facebook and corporate website)
- Brand management and content creation for Facebook and corporate website.
- Implement digital marketing plans and campaigns by coordinating with internal and external stakeholders.
- Influencer outreach to co-promote social campaigns and online marketing activities.
- Develop online and offline marketing campaigns to promote the Citibank brand
- Social media reporting and analysis for insights to judge the effectiveness of the campaign.
- Develop and executed annual marketing plans for credit card branding and promotional tie ups with other businesses.
- Create co-promotion campaigns with leading brands (Club 21, M1, Diesel and FOX)
- Constant monitoring of market trends and performing market research of competitor's products.
- Development of surveys, sales and marketing collaterals to facilitate the sales team

#### **DBS Bank**

DBS is a leading financial services group in Asia. Headquartered in Singapore, with a growing presence in Greater China, Southeast Asia and South Asia.

### **Senior Marketing Executive** (Consumer Banking Group - Strategic Planning and Marketing) Jul 2006 ~ Aug 2008

- Performing market research on competitor's products and current trends in the market.
- Implementing marketing campaigns and strategy for the sales team to generate revenue.
- Implementation and coordination of road shows to promote various new banking products and services.
- Conduct surveys with clients on what areas need improvement with regards to service standards and new product launches.
- Developed and executed annual marketing strategies for new product launches and product branding.
- Creating collaterals for banking products which would be used in the various branches in

DBS.

- Ensure promotions and corporate branding are properly updated on the company website.
- In charge of business analysis and MIS reports for top management.
- Monitoring and analysing the Key Performance Indicators (KPI) of all the various bank branches in DBS.
- Conduct training to the various branch staff with regards to client servicing, sales process and customer restitution.

#### **Wellness** is Ours

Wellness is Ours is a results-focused wellness company based on the unbiased scouring for top solutions. Its product offering include health supplements, therapy devices, and diagnostic machines all recognised within the scientific and medical community.

# Sales and Marketing Manager (Sales and Marketing Department)

Mar 2005 ~ Jul 2006

- Handle B2B sales accounts and develop new accounts for sales of health products and therapy devices
- Understand technical uses of products and devices to customise sales packages for different customers e.g. spas, wellness centres, natural health practitioners
- Manage trade and public exhibitions Hire and train part-time staff, produce marketing materials, coordinate logistics and set-up, and lead sales team
- Handle customer concerns, follow up, obtain feedback and service existing customers
- Plan and coordinate events e.g. health seminars, camps, workshops
- Prepare sales projections, set targets, and carve monthly action plans to achieve them

#### **EDUCATION**

BSc (Hons) in Economics and Management University of London (London School of Economics and Political Science)

#### IT KNOWLEDGE AND COMPUTER SYSTEMS

Microsoft Office – Outlook, Excel, Word, PowerPoint Content Management System (CMS) - Wordpress, Kentico C programming, Computer aided drafting, Computer aided design & Computer aided machining

#### **LANGUAGES**

English (Native)
Chinese (Native)
Thai (professional proficiency)

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Martial Status: Single
Date of Birth: 16 Oct 1979
Nationality: Singaporean